Those who ceaselessly hone the art
of killing are known as masters.
These lethal abilities, dutifully
passed down through many generations,
have become what are
called modified bloodlines.
This is the story of one such master,
Hikaru Gero of the Poison Clan and his
greatest challenge yet, to get married.
No mama, lots of time.
Toxic!
Kill or kiss
Let's go!
Kill a kiss, can't kill a kiss.
Never forget Ghetto, the key
is to size up your target.
Observe the machine, the prize's position.
Note the strength of the
claw's grip and so on.
Then when the moment is right?
You strike!
How complex.
Now you give it a try!
Crane games are evergreen
in the dating world.
The more effortless you
make it look, the better.
Earn a high score in the game of love.
Time to strike.
10,000 yen gone! Then again,
maybe you should steer clear of this
machine until you've had more practice.
Put it in a coin, hey?
That's more my speed.
Watch this.
Spotted garden eels!
Finish!
Perfect!
You're number one! Congratulations!
I admit that was incredible.
But probably won't win you many girls.
Next game!
Let's go.
Why does this exist?
Let's make hunting memories
that'll last a lifetime.
By the way, Gero, speaking of
hunters... Now decorate! Did you hear?
You mean the hitman hunter that's
going around killing masters?
No one knows who or what they
want, but they're no amateur.
Dan the Dismemberer and Kushima
the Spearmaster both got taken out.
Masters are the best assassins out there.
I doubt there are many people who
could take Kushima on head-to-head.
You'd better be careful.
Right.
Aw, it's so cute! All done!
Was this supposed to be fun?
No one likes a party pooper, Gedo.
Then I rescind my comment.
Remember, it's all about the memories.
We're commemorating the
fun both of us had today.
Is that how it works?
Would you like to print out this memory?
You'd be happy, right?
If a girl started talking
about DIY candy kits with you?
Well, yeah.
Don't try forcing a conversation.
But if you can get caught up
in something your date enjoys,
you might be surprised
by how much fun you have.
Guess we should call it a day -
Hikaru Gero, we need to talk.
But before we do, you have
to take a picture with me.
So, Kimi Arashiyama, let
me get this straight.
You want to hire Gero so you've
been following him around?
You could have reached
out on the dark nap.
There hasn't been a babe as
smokin' as me in centuries.
Frankly, you should be honored.
We call that a red flag. Wait!
You should hear me out before
you leave my life forever!
You know, stalking the guy you want
to hire doesn't exactly inspire trust.
You're right. I'm sorry.
For a sec, I was convinced the Hitman
Hunter had come to get Gato. Oh, yeah.
About that.
I'm actually a master, too.
Just like you.
Until someone comes along and
takes care of the hitman hunter.
I'm a target, too.
I'll let you protect me.
Come on, let's go.
You can't leave me!
You said you were a master, right?
So shouldn't you be able
to protect yourself?
I am, but you see, fighting
really isn't my thing.
I think we ought to stay and hear her out.
What?
Seriously?
If Arashiyama went through all this trouble
to seek help from a complete stranger,
she must be in a pretty tight spot.
Right?
Arashiyama?
Arashiyama? Arashiyama? Arashiyama?
Hey!
Hey, Master Hikaru, seriously
being this nice to me?
Look, her face!
Not only that, he's holding me
in his arms, calling out my name.
Actually paying attention to
me is still good to be true!
When I found out the hitman hunter
was after me, I was terrified.
Then as luck would have it,
I meet Master Hikaru Gator.
I didn't even make an appointment.
I bet it's inconvenient, but
he's treating me so courteously.
Arashiyama.
I think she's coming too.
Finally, I receive an
answer to my prayers!
Go ahead and give it your best shot,
sucker, because I'm untouchable!
Just try and take me out, Hitman Hunter!
Well, look, I never said I'd take the job.
Man, her lab sure does carry.
Don't tell me.
You're wondering, just
what kind of master am I?
Let's start over.
My name's Kimi Arashiyama,
the Hamster Master.
This is my partner, Sirius.
I'll have you know, he's the reason
I was able to track you down.
When it comes to intel gathering or
anything that requires a delicate touch,
me and my hamster are the ones to call.
Cuteness overload!
So you're related to the beast clan while
all masters might be
expertly trained killers?
They're not necessarily skilled in combat.
I'm more about assassination
and traps, for instance.
You seriously consider that amateur hour?
For the record,
I didn't want anything
to do with The hitman
hunter but my association
said the hunt was on.
They're all fired up
about taking this jerk!
out.
And you're in danger so you
want a bodyguard? Got it.
Instead of approaching
me why not ask someone
within your own clan to protect you from?
They'd say no.
Up until my great-great-grandpa's
generation we were Ratmasters.
Even the
main Beast Clan respected us so
we had weight to throw around.
But now our bloodline has thinned
out so much I wouldn't be surprised
if we ended up getting stripped
of our master title tomorrow.
I'm not exactly helping things
since I have zero kills.
This collar is the only link I have left.
All the branches of the
Beast Clan must wear them.
So you see how it is.
I show up to association
meetings when they tell me to,
but they've already decided the most
important stuff by the time I've arrived,
like taking on the hunter.
You know what they told me?
A master who doesn't or can't kill.
and works a normal job at a normal company
is only good for being
one thing, a shield.
Thank you for listening.
I've calmed down.
I got carried away earlier, like the future
head of one of the five great families?
would ever guard a branch family nobody.
Plus, there's no way I can
afford your massive fee.
But I got to meet my fave before I died.
10,000 yen a day.
Just need to know when to start.
You're sure about this, Gero?
I mean...
You're in a real bind.
Aren't you?
All right.
I guess it's fine.
This kind of derails my plans.
But at least Gero's charms are
starting to shine through on their own.
I'm proud of him.
I've dreamt of this for so long!
Advice! Help me!
Try hugging her back.
You're kidding!
You know I can't!
Oh, there you are!
Hey!
Okay, Hikaru Gero an assistant?
I'm taking you to meet the
rest of the association.
Plus, they'll find out
about you eventually.
I guess this is the real Arashiyama.
She's the most unhinged woman so far,
but she is a fellow master. Who knows?
The two of them might actually hit it off.
We're here.
I'll handle introductions.
Serpent Master Ryuma.
Owl Master Chojabaru.
Hippo Master Shibaseki.
Orca Master Konkaiji.
Buffalo Master Heart.
Alligator Master Hamawaki.
Sleep on the job?
No, the animals are fine,
but the humans are dead.
Are you with the clan?
What happened?
He's not.
Hurry up!
Both of you, run!
So, uh, you're supposed to
be the poison master, right?
I don't know what you're
doing here, but...
Hey, your timing's perfect!
This saves me from
having to track you down.
You're a big name now!
I can cross you off my list.
Wait!
Did he just?
Stab Ghetto?
Run
Don't stand there!
Go, now!
Any deeper and it could have been fatal.
I've stopped the bleeding.
But it won't last.
So you're the hitman hunter?
What are you after?
He did that?
With one little knife?
This guy's not human!
I can't let this drag out.
Is there enough time to set a trap?
Not a chance.
I've just got to face him head
on and go all out from the start.
Optical reflex accelerator.
Toxin vision.
Muscle reflex enhancer.
Toxin javelin strike.
That double dose should
end this fight fast.
What's up? Huh?
A mistake.
I hear you, but the Poison Master
is still an assassin, right?
He's taking bodyguard
gigs on the Dark Nav?
You sure you've got the right guy?
No one in the five families
would be caught dead doing that.
The thing is, he seems dangerous.
He shot two syringes into
his own neck. Two! I know.
Seems kind of risky, letting him go.
I feel it's probably for
the best if I take him out.
Yeah.
I'll beat him to the punch.
No way.
Toxic Vision's not able
to keep track of him?
That was a close one.
You guys okay?
Got a soft spot for animals, huh?
I mean, it's not like
they did anything wrong.
Where did you come from?
A branch of the Iron Clan?
I'm pretty sure I'm just a normal guy.
Impossible.
Which family sent you?
Man, why would I lie to
somebody who's about to die?
All of my relatives are teachers.
In that case, he's got to be a mutant.
Masters spend generations
building up their bloodlines,
but somehow this freak has
surpassed them in only one.
For lunch pretty soon
damn it I've never tried
this before but I've got
no choice toxin triple dose
Yikes come on why did you
go and do that it's suicide
I should have known a triple
dose might have worked
if I hadn't already lost so much blood.
What did I tell you?
You killed so many people.
After all the hatred you
spread, this is what you get.
Time to die.
Just promise me one thing.
You won't touch either of them.
Swear it.
Yo, Hitman Hunter!
Gator's not dying on my watch!
The rules just did a 180!
Uh, if you get in the way, I've
got to take care of you, too.
Big dummy, shove it!
You think he's going
around spreading hatred?
Like hell he is!
He offered to be my bodyguard,
even when I couldn't pay him!
I wasn't gonna go down at
the shield for some jerk!
But I'm more than happy
to die for my idol!
Serious squad?
Ready?
Modify bloodline plus plus Feel the
wrath of Pontus Major unleashed?
The greater dog that
shines in the winter sky!
How do you like that, punk?
Where do you think you're taking him?
Let go.
What do you mean?
Obviously the hospital,
since he's dying and all.
You mean Canis Major actually worked?
You were dead set on killing me.
Why save my life?
Mmm.
I've never seen that before.
Masters looking out for each other.
Plus, I don't feel like
killing you anymore.
Those are my reasons.
Good enough for you?
I see.
Put me down.
But your wounds...
...are something I can handle myself.
My name's Pichi Nakagawa.
When's it my turn to
have his head on my lap?
I have one goal.
Eliminating the Beast Clan, one of
the five great families for good.
Rumor is they're planning something major,
something dangerous that'll
kill a whole lot of people.
I figured I'd take them out
before the damage got out of hand.
Then how come you're hunting
people outside of their clan?
I might as well. Come again?
See, I had no idea where
to even start looking,
so I asked anyone who could
steer me in the right direction.
Which led me to a homicidal
maniac they once did a deal with.
Then there was the guy
with the pointy stick.
Plus those six from the branch families.
They weren't much help, but it's
not like I could let them go.
Wait, what maniac?
Dan the Dismemberer He
didn't work for money.
He took apart old men as payment.
And Kushima the Spearmaster
He had a reputation
for involving innocent
bystanders in his jobs?
All I want is to open a
cafe with my girlfriend.
But before I can do that, somebody
needs to clean up the world.
Our poor customers.
How could they relax?
Why is his head still on her lap?
Feuding with one of the
five great families?
Are you nuts? What?
No, but wouldn't it be better without
these bad guys to worry about?
Normally, I'd write that off as a fantasy.
But with his abilities, he
might be able to pull it off.
Out of nowhere, there's you.
I heard the family of
Poison Masters was bad.
But it turns out you're different.
Obviously, you're not dangerous.
At least not to the world I want.
Not right now.
But maybe that'll change.
So, uh, that means you're gonna
let us go, right? Come on!
Well, problem solved, then!
Mr.
Gato, you're from one
of the five families.
Maybe you can tell me what
the Beast Clan is up to.
Not like I'd know anything.
People call us the five great
families out of convenience.
It's not like we have
any sort of connection.
That's too bad.
And what about you?
You're a branch of the Beast Clan.
Any leads?
I've never been to the main
house or met the family.
That figures.
All I know is I have the collar
they give all the branch members.
Arashiyama!
A bat?
What's wrong with her, Kato?
I don't know.
I'm guessing it's this collar.
Easy.
I wouldn't remove that unless you
wanted to completely drain a toast.
The Bonda Constrictor is a living
accessory engineered to suck blood.
I went ahead and activated it, meaning
that woman's got three days to live, tops.
Why make her aware?
Wouldn't want him running off, would we?
The livestock, that is.
Spare me the death glare!
If you're actually interested in facing
me, Hikaru Gero and Piichi Nakagawa,
here's your invitation.
See me on the Beast Clan's
home turf, Dogo Animal Kingdom!
I'll be crazy.
Oh, make that noise.
Oh, I'll be crazy.
Ah, the
out-to-na-ni-yo-i-wata-si-bick-ri-dottk-ri-fum-da-ri-ke-t-ri-muh-ga-muchu.
Ah,
out-to-na-ni-yo-i-an-ata-hattari-ba-kari-un-zari-gakari-bye-bye-chu.
I can't see it.
I can't see it. I can't see it.
Thank you
so
much
for joining us.
This is 100 % a trap, for sure!
This is what somebody who's
as good as mine can do!
Absolutely delicious.
Next time, the Animal Kingdom.